Hello everyone. This is Ema Sakurai, reporter for the Nighttime Brunch Entertainment Corner.
This time I would like to interview a certain person.
Let's go!
Hello.
First of all, please introduce yourself.
Yes, I'm Yuna Nakamura, the number 17 in Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku. I'm Yuna Nakamura, the number 17 in Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku. I look forward to working with you.
Please introduce yourself.
Yuna Nakamura, you are going to perform in Yoruen Land vol. 4, please tell us how you feel now.
I am in the middle of rehearsal, and I am practicing a lot of things right now, such as shields, dancing, singing, and acting,
I am sure this will be a fun song, so please come and see it.
I'm sure it will be a fun song, so please come and see it.
I would like to ask Ina Nakamura some questions,
First of all, I would like to know your charm point.
Is it a charm point?
Yes, I do.
Hmmm.
Eyes, sorry, my nose is itchy.
I have an itchy nose.
Please go ahead.
And, I like it because I get complimented a lot.
You sure do have big, dull eyes.
Which one is it?
Which one?
I felt that you have big beautiful eyes.
Thank you very much. I'm glad.
So, Yuna, you said that your charm point is your eyes.
Well, I would like to ask you the next question right away,
It has been a little over a year since you entered a private ABS junior high school,Yuna, it has been just over a year since you entered ABS Junior High School,
If you were to use one kanji character to describe the appeal of ABS Junior High School, what would it be?
It's difficult to say.
I wonder.
Strange.
Strange. Is it "strange" as in "change"?
Change.
How about that?
The group is changing in many ways, but there are also many strange songs,
We are all very interesting and strange people, so it is strange.
Weird. Strange.
Strange as in change.
Indeed. We are a group that is changing in many ways, aren't we?
Yes, we are.
I see.
Then, what should I do?
If you were going to live abroad, where would you live?
Hmmm...
I wonder.
But I went to New Zealand recently for a location shoot and a live concert,
And I really enjoyed New Zealand,
You understand, don't you?
I can understand.
I can't wait to go back to New Zealand because the food and the cities are so beautiful and delicious,
I have been to New Zealand only once before,
I have only been to New Zealand.
If I wanted to live in New Zealand, I would choose New Zealand.
I see. That sounds great.
Then, I will go back a little more. I will go a little further.Then I'll go a little more. I'll go a little further.
I hear that you have been working hard on your cooking lately.
My specialty is clam chowder.
Clamchada! Clam chada! That's amazing.
Thank you very much.
Do you make it yourself from scratch?
I used to make it with a roux for clam chowder, but when I went to the supermarket the other day, they didn't have any roux.
I tried making it myself without roux, but it turned out surprisingly well, so I've recently gotten into it. I prefer to make it with soy milk.
Wow, it looks delicious. It looks amazing.
Please let me try it. I'd love to.
Yes, I will definitely make it.
Thank you very much.
But I couldn't cook in the first place.
It was like I couldn't slice cabbage anymore.
Oh, you were saying something like that.
Anyway, I wanted to shred cabbage,
I put shredded cabbage in miso soup and everything.
I don't shred cabbage in miso soup.
It is surprisingly tasty.
Yes, it is.
I couldn't even use a knife properly,
Before I knew it, I was making clam chowder,
I always make what I know how to make.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Now that you have learned a lot about Eina Nakamura, I would like to close this interview with a very cute comment from Eina Nakamura,
I would like to close with one extremely cute comment from Eina Nakamura.
Please let me close with one extremely cute comment from Eina Nakamura.Now, please.
Mmm.
Great.
No good.
I'm so nervous. Being out this close to the microphone like this. Yes, it is.
Yes, it is. Why are you such a drawl? No, no, no, no. Even the super cute closing statement.
Oh, yes.
Yuna, I'll do my best. Next is the nighttime land. And then there's the big show at Ebichu, so if you're interested, definitely, definitely, definitely come and see me. I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
It's the best.
Thank you very much.